本字幕由NEW字幕组译制
仅供英语交流学习使用  严禁用于商业途径
NEW字幕组招新群：720899169
快来加入我们  欢乐做剧
翻译: SelinaG  ringo  Sunny的剁椒苹果  沈格子  白糖锅盔  西比鹅  没戴眼镜听不清  平果猫
时间轴: 柴  柠檬  汪鹅鹅
校对: 耳屎可以吃  Katerina
总监: 耳屎可以吃
《小谢尔顿》前情提要
Previously on Young Sheldon...
我们已经聊了橄榄球和孙辈
Well, we've covered football and grandkids...
我们可能把能说的都说完了
Maybe we've run out of stuff to talk about.
我们还没聊你的前夫
We forgot about your ex-husband.
就是和你约会的那个人
The one you're dating.
我知道不要在下冰雹的时候招惹他
Well, I know not to piss him off during a hailstorm.
他有没有告诉你
Well, did he tell you that
我被他锁在门外的时候没穿衣服
I was naked when he locked me out?
你在下冰雹的时候
What were you doing naked
裸拿高尔夫球杆是想干嘛
with a golf club in a hailstorm?
你懂的  那时候是七十年代
Ah, you know, it was the '70s.
就想跟你说下我看了你的论文
I was just calling to let you know I read your paper.
你那中微子的质量是不可能的
The masses for your neutrinos are impossible.
我从零开始重写了整篇论文
I completely rewrote the whole thing from scratch.
我知道感谢名单是按首字母排序的
I know credits are usually listed alphabetically,
但你要把我放第二  我也没意见
but I'm completely fine with my name going second.
我不会把你的名字放上去的
I'm not putting your name on it in any way.
格兰特·林克莱特
Grant Linkletter.
斯特奇斯博士盗取了我的成果
Dr. Sturgis has stolen my work
用在自己的论文里
and is using it in his own paper.
你怎么敢指控我剽窃
How dare you accuse me of plagiarism!
你再也不要来上我的课了
I don't want to see you in my class anymore.
好的  斯特奇斯博士
I see, Dr. Sturgis.
对  那种行为的确难以原谅
Yes, that is unforgivable behavior.
好的  再见
Okay. Bye.
他道歉了吗
Did he apologize?
没有  他对你很失望
No. He is very upset with you.
我对他也很失望
Well, I'm upset with him.
那你也不能
That doesn't excuse you from trying
跟林克莱特博士举报他啊
to get him in trouble by calling Dr. Linkletter.
那我还能和谁打小报告
Who else was I supposed to tattle to?
他妈妈应该已经不在了
I doubt his mother's still alive.
谢尔顿  我懂你为什么不开心
Sheldon, I understand why you're upset,
但你还是欠他一个道歉
but you still owe him an apology.
那你就是不懂
Then you don't understand.
现阶段  你俩还是
Well, for now, it sounds like you two
各自冷静的好
could use a little quiet time.
好吧  那我转去林克莱特博士的班
Fine. I'll switch over to Dr. Linkletter's class.
他比斯特奇斯博士高一个头
He's a foot taller than Sturgis
能在黑板上写的更多
and can reach more of the chalkboard.
我的意思是
What I meant was...
也许暂时先别去大学上课了
maybe it's time to take a break from your college classes.
什么  为什么  我可是全优
What? Why? I've gotten straight As.
我知道大学的课难不倒你
I know you're smart enough for college.
我只是不确定你是否够成熟
I'm just not sure you're mature enough.
显然你已经把我逼入绝境
Well, it appears you've backed me into a corner.
我现在想发脾气
I would throw a tantrum right now,
但那样就证明你是对的
but that would just prove your point.
你去哪
Where are you going?
玩火车去
To play with my trains.
可能听起来幼稚  但很多老男人也有这爱好
Which may sound immature, but it's a hobby many old men enjoy.
*要说强壮我第一*
*Nobody else is stronger than I am*
*昨日移山无人敌*
*Yesterday I moved a mountain*
*你的英雄就是我*
*I bet I could be your hero*
*小小身躯大智慧*
*I am a mighty little man.*
《小谢尔顿》
第三季  第十八集
你应该只盯着我这个啦啦队员看
I'm the only cheerleader you should be looking at.
嗨  我正在找你
Oh. Hi. Oh, I was trying to find you.
-只是来祝你比赛顺利  -谢谢
- Just wanted to wish you a good game. - Thank you.
我会为你加油的
I'm gonna be cheering for you.
-棒  -除非被我发现你在看别人
- Great. - Unless I catch you looking at someone else.
那我绝对饶不了你
Then you'll regret it.
我可没开玩笑
I'm not kidding.
嗨  乔治
Hi, George.
嗨  哈钦斯小姐
Hey, Ms. Hutchins.
你以前好像没来看过比赛
I don't think I've ever seen you at a game before.
今天是周五嘛  我答应了医生
Well, it's Friday, and I promised my therapist
会每周尝试一样新事物的
I'd try one new thing a week.
所以这周你选了橄榄球  不错啊
And you picked football. Good for you.
谢尔顿不在这儿吗
I don't suppose Sheldon's here?
是啊  他不太喜欢户外运动
Nah, he doesn't much care for outdoor sports.
也不喜欢运动
Or sports.
也不喜欢户外
Or the outdoors.
我还想着能不能找个人陪我坐着
I was hoping I'd have someone to sit with.
-不好意思了  -没事
- Sorry. - That's okay.
我就不该心存希望
It was my fault for letting myself feel hope.
欢迎你待在场边看球
You're welcome to watch from the sidelines.
谢了
Thanks.
局外人一样看着生命流逝
Watching life go by from the sidelines
是我的作风
is kind of my thing.
小心啊
Hey, heads up!
我的天  你还好吗
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
不太好
I don't think so.
快叫救护车
Call an ambulance.
别担心  你会没事的
Don't worry, we're gonna get you taken care of.
要是我死了  告诉我的心理医生我恨他
If I die, tell my therapist I hate him.
谁说人要成熟才能读大学
And who says you have to be mature to go to college?
我看过《动物屋》[关于大学的喜剧片]
I've seen Animal House.
-是吗  -至少我看过海报
- You have? - Well, I've seen the poster.
那些人可不是什么上大学的料
Those people are not college material.
小可爱  我知道这话你不爱听
Moon pie, I know you don't like to hear this,
但人生中总有些事情
but there are some things in life
你要到一定年纪了才能明白
that can only be learned in time.
那你肯定啥都懂了  是吧
So you must have learned them all, huh?
给我出去
Get out of my house.
梅德福社区医院
急诊
-挺住啊  -挺着呢
- Hang in there. - I'm hangin'.
这可是个了不得的经历  可以讲给孙辈听
Hey, this will be quite a story to tell your grandkids, huh?
我独居  单身
I live alone. I'm single.
我觉得我不太可能会有孙辈了
I don't think grandkids are in the picture.
这个...
Oh. Well, I...
我有老婆孩子  但
I got a wife, kids. It's...
也挺不省心的
It's overrated.
然后我妈妈说
And then my mother said
我还太小  不适合上大学
I wasn't mature enough for college.
你敢信吗
Can you believe that?
当然
Absolutely.
所以你也觉得他们是对的
So you're on their side, too?
我是越南人  在我的文化里
I'm Vietnamese. In my culture,
只要爸妈还在
until your parents die,
那就还是个孩子
you're basically a baby.
真的吗
Really?
我奶奶就还是把我爸当孩子
My grandmother still treats my dad like a child.
吃饭的时候  奶奶不坐  他就不能坐
At dinner, he can't sit until she sits,
奶奶没问话  他就不能说话
and he can't speak until he's spoken to.
那我真庆幸我不是越南人
Well, I'm glad I'm not Vietnamese.
现实更加恐怖
It's not as fun as I make it look.
那可不能把她一个人丢在家里
Well, you can't bring her home to an empty apartment.
把她带回家来吧  我们来照顾她
Bring her here, and we'll look after her
直到她好起来为止
until she's back on her feet.
你确定
You sure?
当然
Of course.
我们让她住乔治的房间
We'll set her up in Georgie's room.
谢谢你  玛丽  一会儿见
Thanks, Mare. See you in a bit.
乔治
Hey, George.
你能这么照顾她  可真好
It's real nice of you, taking care of her like this.
我也有错
Well, it was kinda my fault.
也有错  这全都是你的错
Kinda? It was all your fault.
再见
Bye.
我们战况如何
Hey. How'd we do?
-你什么都没错过  -那么惨吗
- You didn't miss anything. - That bad?
我可以肯定地说  你已经看到今晚最精彩的一击
I can safely say you saw the best hit of the night.
她怎么样了
How's she doing?
还行
Well, not bad.
幸好
Could be worse.
头部轻微受损
A little whiplash,
肋骨几处擦伤
couple of bruised ribs,
胳膊断了...
broken arm...
还有锁骨
and collarbone.
就这些了
But that's it.
刚才真是太逗了  你跳开了
Pretty funny how you jumped out of the way
她被撞倒了
and let her get clobbered.
我才没有跳开
I did not jump out of the way!
你跳了
Oh, yeah, you did.
他们都给你录下来了
They got you on tape.
好吧
Okay, fine.
但那只是条件反射
But that was pure instinct.
况且  她也不应该站在场边
Besides, she shouldn't have been standing on the sidelines.
她站那干什么
Why was she there?
我让她站的
I told her she could.
你一定内疚到不行吧
Oh, man, you must feel terrible.
当然
Yeah, of course I do.
这你可是全责啊
I mean, it's all on you.
你说完了吗
You done?
不  宝贝  我才刚刚开始呢
Oh-ho-ho, baby, I'm just getting started.
小可怜  快进来
Oh, you poor dear. Come on in.
谢谢  希望我没给你添太多麻烦
Thanks. I hope I'm not putting you out.
当然没有
Of course not.
你好  谢尔顿
Hi, Sheldon.
你敢信吗  我妈说我不能去大学上课了
Can you believe my mother said I can't go to college?
你们没跟我商量就让她住我房间了
So you just put her in my room without consulting me?
跟你商量
Consulting you?
谁管你怎么想的
Who cares what you think?
我不睡沙发
Well, I ain't gonna sleep on the couch.
就几天
It's just for a few nights
等她能照顾自己就行
until she can take care of herself.
至少让我去外婆那住呗
Can I at least stay at Meemaw's?
只要你保证再也不回来了
If you promise not to come back.
你干嘛对我这么刻薄
Why you got to be so mean to me?
我喜欢
It just feels right.
斯特奇斯博士用了我的计算方式
And then after Dr. Sturgis incorporated my math,
论文作者却不愿意加我名字
he refused to give me a coauthor credit.
谢尔顿  她并不想听这些
Sheldon, she doesn't want to hear about that.
没关系
It's okay.
你骨头断的时候  你听见碎裂声了吗
So, when your bones broke, did you hear a crunch?
没有
No.
-我爸给你做人工呼吸了吗  -没有
- Did my dad have to give you mouth-to-mouth? - No.
我不知道我妈妈是怎么亲他的
I don't know how my mom kisses him.
接下来  大家看这个玫瑰...
Next up, we have this rose..
谁会买这种垃圾啊
Who buys this crap?
三杯啤酒下肚的我
Me, after three beers.
你看这个鬼玩意儿
I mean, look at this damn thing.
我当时在想啥呢
What was I thinking?
我能问你一个私人问题吗
Can I ask you a personal question?
遗嘱没你份
You're not in my will.
是我的女朋友的事
It's about my girlfriend.
不是啦
Nothing bad.
只是我和简已经约会一阵子了
It's just, I've been seeing Jana for a while now, and
我还挺喜欢她的
I like her fine...
但我觉得她的认真程度  超出了我的预期
but it feels like she's getting more serious than I want to be.
乔治  除非你结婚
Georgie, until you're married,
不然谁都没法捆死你
you are not tied down to anybody.
你可以继续做任何想做的事
You just go ahead and do whatever you want.
广阔天地  尽情享乐
Play the field. Have some fun.
有点意思
Interesting.
戴尔也是这么说的
That's what Dale said, too.
是吗
Oh, did he?
是啊
Yeah.
我男朋友
My boyfriend?
没错
Yeah.
我要是不去上大学
If I don't go to college,
我该干什么呢
what am I supposed to do?
整天呆在高中吗
Spend all my days in high school?
那得多惨啊
How sad is that?
是挺惨
Pretty sad.
你总是那么理解我
You always did get me.
看来你是被人误解了
Sounds like you're feeling misunderstood.
没错  被斯特奇斯博士  还有我妈妈
I am... by Dr. Sturgis, my mother,
可能还有整个越南文化
and possibly the entire Vietnamese culture.
你知道我现在有点疼吗
Do you understand that I'm in a little bit of pain right now?
不好意思  我应该表现出同情的
Oh, I'm sorry. I should be exhibiting compassion.
等等  我能嗷得更好
Wait, I can do better.
嗷得不错
Nailed it.
该吃止痛药了
It's time for your pain pill.
小心点  你可能会上瘾
Be careful. You could become addicted
然后丢掉工作
and lose your job.
那是你仅有的一切了
Which is all you have.
赶紧出去吧你
Get out of here.
谢谢
Thank you.
你感觉还好吗
You-you comfortable?
还需要点什么吗
Can I get you anything else?
不用了  我感觉还行
No. I-I'm okay.
你人真的太好了  还把我带回家
You've been so kind to welcome me into your home.
只是些力所能及的事
Well, it's the least we could do.
待在这样的家庭太幸福了
It's so nice to be around a family like this.
我一个人生活太久了
I've been alone for... so long.
说实话  除了猫  我身边一个人都没有
Honestly, if it weren't for the cats, I'd have no one.
等等  我的猫
Oh, wait. The cats!
Edgar Allan Poe  埃德加·爱伦·坡
创建侦探小说  恐怖小说
我抛弃了埃德加和爱伦
I abandoned Edgar and Allan.
埃德加和爱伦
Edgar and Allan?
坡逃跑了
Poe ran away.
能不能麻烦你去喂它们  顺便传达我的爱
Would you please go feed them and tell them I love them?
能不能等到明天早上
Any chance this could wait till morning?
应该可以吧
I guess.
你要去哪儿
Where you off to?
喂猫
Cats!
你觉得他在和别人约会吗
So you think he's seeing somebody else?
我觉得我不该说这些
I don't think I should be talking about this.
-他是我老板  -他还是我男朋友呢  快说
- He's my boss. - Well, he's my boyfriend, so spill it.
老年人说男朋友这个词真怪
It's weird when old people say "Boyfriend."
行吧  我爱人
Fine. My lover.
更怪了
Well, that's worse.
赶快说
Then talk!
我只见过他和前妻在一起
The only woman I've really seen him with is his ex-wife.
是嘛  但他恨她
Oh, yeah, but he hates her.
看起来不像啊
Don't seem like it.
你这话什么意思
What do you mean by that?
-他们看起来很和睦  -有多和睦
- They seem friendly. - How friendly?
-不知道  他对她挺好的  -有多好
- I don't know. He's nice to her. - How nice?!
不好意思  我正看电视呢
Do you mind? I'm trying to watch this.
看看这个小家伙
Now look at this little guy...
小混蛋
Son of a bitch!
别跑  埃德加  或者爱伦
Here! Edgar! Or Allan.
不管是哪一只
Whichever the hell one you are.
他们有没有一起离开店子
They ever leave the store together?
我能去睡了吗
Can I please just go to bed?
先回答我的问题
Just answer the damn question.
我可能会因此被开除的
I feel like I'm gonna get fired for this.
乔吉  别担心
Georgie, don't worry.
我不会告诉别人的
Anything you say is gonna stay right here.
但你总是撒谎
But you lie all the time.
我就是跟你学会撒谎的
I learned to lie from you.
看我们的关系多奇妙啊
See what a special bond we have?
现在回答我的问题
Now answer the damn question!
你怎么去了这么久
Why were you gone for so long?
别说了
I don't want to talk about it.
内赠鬼魂探测器
和朋友一起玩吧
这是什么
What's that?
这是麦片里送的鬼魂探测器
It's a ghost detector that came in my cereal box.
这就是张纸
It's just a piece of paper.
那它为什么会动
Then why did it move in my hand?
因为你在出汗
From perspiration.
或者因为有鬼
Or ghosts.
早啊
Mornin'.
你去看哈钦斯女士了吗
Did you check on Ms. Hutchins?
她还活着吗
Is she still alive?
当然  为这么这么问
Of course she is. Why?
没事
No reason.
我去和她一起吃早餐
I'm gonna go eat my breakfast with her.
谢尔顿  让她休息吧
Sheldon, just let her rest.
没事的  有我陪伴她很开心
It's okay. She enjoys my company.
另外  她能理解我为什么和斯特奇斯博士闹矛盾
Also, she understands what I'm going through with Dr. Sturgis.
什么
Excuse me.
我是在帮助你
I am just trying to help you grow up
长大成人
to be a functional adult.
帮我  你女儿还在找谷物鬼魂呢
Me? This one's looking for cereal ghosts.
而且我找到了
Looking for and found 'em.
我不管  你还不适合去上大学
I don't care. You are not ready for college.
如果都听你的  我现在还在上小学呢
If it were up to you, I'd still be in grade school.
你以为这样很成熟吗  并不是
If you think this is mature behavior, it isn't!
当妈很难  对吧
Being a mom's hard, isn't it?
偶尔吧
Sometimes.
如果你想找人倾诉
If you ever want to talk about it,
有我呢
I'm here for you.
它又动了
Ooh, it's moving again.
你真幸运
You're so lucky.
告诉我怎么个幸运法
You're gonna have to walk me through that.
你家里可没人告诉你
Well, you don't have anyone in your house telling you
该做什么  不该做什么
what you can or can't do.
是的  谢尔顿
Right, Sheldon.
我无依无靠
I don't have anyone.
我就是这个意思
I just said that.
你已经药物上瘾了吗
Are you becoming a drug addict already?
早上好
Mornin'.
来点希普利甜甜圈和咖啡
Got you some Shipley's Do-Nuts and coffee.
你的脸怎么了
What happened to your face?
不是埃德加抓的就是爱伦
either Edgar or Allan.
是埃德加
Oh, that was Edgar.
他淘气的很
He can be a rascal.
-早上好  -早上好
- Good mornin'. - Mornin'.
-你睡得好吗  -还行
- Did you sleep good? - Yeah.
要来点薄烤饼吗
Want some pancakes?
好啊
Sure.
就多问一句戴尔的事儿
Just one more question about Dale.
拜拜
Bye.
就这样
There we go.
切成小块  一口一个
Nice little bite-size pieces.
谢谢  乔治
Thanks, George,
但我能自己来
but I-I think I can manage.
不不  这是我的荣幸
No, no. My pleasure.
他内疚得不行  你说什么他都会乖乖听话
He feels so guilty, he'll do anything you ask him.
你说的够多了
That's enough from you.
他关车门夹了我的手
He bought me an Easy-Bake Oven
给我买了个烤炉玩具来赔罪
when he closed the car door on my thumb.
不像我妈  伤害了她的孩子
Unlike my mother, who feels no guilt
却不感到内疚
after hurting her children.
你好大胆子
How dare you.
我在保护你
I am trying to keep you safe
直到你有能力做出成人的决定
until such a time as you can make adult decisions.
我现在就行
I can make them now.
注意点  我们有客人
Hey, hey. We have a guest.
让我们假装相亲相爱呗
Let's pretend like we like each other.
玛丽  饭前祷告吧
Mare, do your grace thing.
你能接受墨西哥菜吧
You okay with Mexican?
还行  挺好
Oh, yeah. Terrific.
那就好
All right.
回家路上可以吃杂物箱里的抗胃酸咀嚼钙片
Now, I got Tums in the glove box for the ride home.
太棒了
Great.
你最近和朱恩联系吗
So, you talk to June lately?
最近几天没有  怎么了
Uh, not in a couple of days. Why?
随便问问
Oh, no reason.
我只是想给她打个电话
I was just kind of thinking about calling her myself.
如果你不介意的话
I mean, if you're okay with that.
和我前妻打电话  想打就打呗
You want to call my ex-wife, go ahead.
打吧
Call her.
我不想让你觉得不舒服
Well, I wouldn't want you to feel uncomfortable.
我看你是想
Yeah, you would.
被你说中了
Yeah, I would.
看到你们相处得那么好我很开心
I think it's nice that y'all get along as well as you do.
说这些是什么意思
Where are we going with this?
没有啦  就随便聊聊
Oh, just nothing. Makin' conversation.
好吧
Okay.
你们睡一起了吗
You sleeping with her?
老天啊  才不会
Lord, no.
她是我前妻啊  拜托
She's my ex-wife. Come on.
我的天  什么变态会跟他前妻睡一起啊
Oh, my gosh, what kind of sicko sleeps with their ex-wife?
这话从何说起啊
Where is this coming from?
-你是嫉妒了吗  -没
- Are you jealous? - No.
我就是想知道
I'd just like to know, you know,
咱们的关系到底到哪一步了
what kind of relationship we're in.
我们还可以各自跟别人约会吗
I mean, are we seeing other people or what?
康妮·塔克
Connie Tucker,
你是要和我稳定交往吗
are you asking me to go steady?
别装傻了  魂淡
You know what I'm asking, jackass.
好吧好吧
All right, all right, all right.
听仔细了  我现在72岁了
You listen to me. Now, I'm 72 years old.
你觉得我还有那个耐性
Do you think I have enough stamina
去跟别的女人耍吗
to go playing around with other women?
你意思是  你跟我在一起
You saying the only reason you're seeing me
是因为你又老又累跟别人处不来了
is you're too old and tired to see anybody else?
给我拿下胃酸片
Give me the Tums.
真想跟你接吻到天荒地老
I could kiss you forever.
那时间有点长啊
That's kind of a long time.
怎么的  你有别的安排啊
You got somewhere else to be?
不啊  就是
No. It's just that,
早晚咱俩都会饿的啊
eventually, we're gonna get hungry.
我怎么总觉得你好像不太喜欢这样啊
Why do I keep getting the feeling you're not into this?
我可喜欢了
Oh, I am into this.
但是呢
But?
我是说我们还年轻  谁知道以后会怎样呢
I mean, we're real young, and who knows what's gonna happen?
我知道  你也应该知道
I know. And you should, too.
别难过啊
Don't feel bad.
我不知道的事可多了
I don't know lots of stuff.
正好咱们在聊这个
So, as long as we're on the subject,
你有跟别人约过会吗
are you seeing anybody else?
没啊
No.
那那个疯教授呢
How about that nutty professor?
我们只是朋友
We're just friends.
好吧  我跟朱恩也是
Yeah, well, that's what June and I are...
就是朋友
Just friends.
那我们算什么
So what are we?
不知道
I don't know.
你想怎么形容
What do you want to call it?
我觉得吧
I guess, a...
固定的伴侣关系
committed relationship.
可以啊  我看行
Mm. Works for me.
那行
Okay.
那就这么定了
It's settled.
康妮
Connie.
这种关系让我感到窒息
This relationship is suffocating me.
我说啥了
What'd I say?
你觉得我配不上你
I'm not enough for you.
我没这么说啊
I didn't say that.
说实话吧
Just be honest.
你就是想跟别的女孩约会
You want to date other girls.
我不想跟别的女孩约会[来取代你]
I don't want to date other girls instead of you,
只是  也跟别人试试看
just... in addition to you.
去死吧你
Drop dead.
好吧  但是我会跟着你  确保你安全到家的
Okay, but I'm gonna follow you and make sure you get home safe!
随便你
Do whatever you want.
如果你去冰激凌店  我给你买暴风杯
If you walk to Dairy Queen, I'll buy you a Blizzard.
要我放点音乐吗
Want me to turn on some music?
这太好吃了  玛丽
Well, this is just delicious, Mary.
谢谢
Thank you.
切的大小合适吗
Bite-sized enough for you?
很完美
Oh. Perfect.
我还得坐在这儿生多久闷气
How long do I have to sit here and sulk
才会有人问我怎么了
before someone asks me what's wrong?
也许大家都听厌了
Maybe people are tired of hearing about it.
哈钦斯女士  你能附和我一下吗
Ms. Hutchins, would you care to chime in?
我不想介入家庭问题  但是
I-I don't want to get in the middle of a family issue, but...
我想说  我曾经和很亲近的人
I will say that I once had a falling out
闹翻过
with someone very close to me.
发生了什么
What happened?
我们最后分道扬镳了
We ended up parting ways on bad terms.
我现在还很后悔
I-I still regret it.
但当时你是对的  他们错了
But you were right and they were wrong?
你知道吗  这已经不重要了
You know what, it doesn't feel like it matters anymore.
我没有哪一天不想念他们的
And not a day goes by that I don't miss them.
也许我的确该给斯特奇斯博士道歉
Perhaps I do owe Dr. Sturgis an apology.
我刚说的是你妈妈
I was talking about your mother.
我回头再跟她道歉
I'll circle back to her.
谢谢
Thank you.
真不敢相信你说通了他
I can't believe you got through to him.
乐意效劳
Happy to help.
你跟谁吵过架
So, who was the person you had the fight with?
我的猫  坡
It was my cat, Poe.
我换了干猫粮之后她跑了
She ran away when I switched to dry food.
干猫粮更便宜
It was cheaper.
-晚安  宝贝  -晚安  妈妈
- Good night, baby. - Night, Mama.
我很抱歉  妈妈
I'm really sorry, Mom.
我原谅你
I forgive you.
但你和斯特奇斯博士和好了
But just because you straightened things out with Dr. Sturgis
不代表你可以回大学上课
doesn't mean you're going back to college.
-我可以  -你不行
- Yes, it does. - No, it doesn't.
你知道你这是在破坏我们的关系吧
I hope you know you're jeopardizing our relationship.
我愿意冒这个险
I will take that risk.
晚安
Good night.
你知道我总会说服你的
You know I'll eventually wear you down.
走着瞧吧
We'll see.
我很难搞的
I'm pretty tough.
我最终说服了她
I eventually wore her down.
毕竟我可不是谁都受得住的
There's just so much of me anybody can take.
本地新闻  周五晚的足球赛上
In local news, Friday night's football game
发生了一起残忍的事故
was marred by a brutal injury,
橄榄球教练乔治·库伯为了保全自己
when football coach George Cooper saved himself
牺牲了受人爱戴的校图书管理员谢丽尔·哈钦斯
at the expense of beloved school librarian Cheryl Hutchins.
糟糕
Oh, no.
温馨提示  下面的片段惨不忍睹
We warn you, the following footage is hard to watch.
那就别播啊
Well, then, don't show it.
让我们再看一遍慢动作回放
Let's see it again in slow motion.
这根本不是新闻
This is not news.